Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/monamoore-072046260 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Business Development Support Sales cold messaging

Mona Moore

"Aspiring BDR/SDR @ RE:WORK TRAINING |Artist|Cook|Educator| Mom of 3 |Next Generation of SaaS Sales Talent"

Poughkeepsie, New York, United States

Summary

Exciting news! I'm embarking on a new adventure in the tech industry as a BDR!

My journey has taught me the importance of personal and professional growth, fueled by values such as spirituality, honesty, loyalty, hard work, and family. I find solace in art, which allows me to explore depth and meaning. Volunteering has been my way of giving back and fostering courage, humility, and patience. With a unique blend of determination, empathy, and humor, I've built strong relationships along the way. Let's connect and see how my diverse strengths can add value to your team!

Experience

RE:WORK TRAINING BDR Candidate July 2023 - Present (10 months) Poughkeepsie, New York

Re:Work Training, a 501(c)3 nonprofit organization, is creating workplaces that reflect the diversity of our neighborhoods.

As a BDR Candidate, I help RE:Work scale their impact by genera qualified prospects through my participation in their 12 week Tech Sales Training Program, including: -Generate outbound leads and handle inbound leads for the company's 8-week Tech Sales Training Program, Donor Program & Corporate Partnership Program -Qualify and develop a robust sales pipeline for RE:Work's spectrum of programming-Schedule and conduct sales calls and demos -Work closely with sales and marketing teams to develop regular strategic plans to meet the company's monthly, quarterly and annual goals - Maintain and update prospect records in our CRM to ensure accurate reports - Communicate and Identify areas of improvement in the sales process

Poughkeepsie City School District
Teaching Assistant
September 2022 - Present (1 year 8 months)
Poughkeepsie, New York, United States

Mount Vernon City School District
Teaching Assistant/Lunch Monitor

January 2018 - September 2022 (4 years 9 months)

Mount Vernon, New York, United States

Herbalife
Sales Representative
February 2020 - September 2020 (8 months)
United States

Education

Woodlands High School

Activity

04/18/2024, Imeila Fonua added candidate to BDR- Test Sample